PATRICK BALDWIN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER \$5178986963

• DETAILS •

5178986963 pbaldwi3@gmail.com

LINKS

Personal Website

• SKILLS •

Rest Web APIs

SQL Server

.NET

React

Angular

Docker

PROFILE

I have a passion for joining complex business problems with creative technology solutions. I love to learn new skills, level up the people around me, and deliver high-quality products that provide meaningful value. I have spent the last 2 years working on a web application used to fund hundreds of billions of dollars of mortgage loans in 2021 and am looking for the next challenge.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Engineer at Rocket Mortgage, Detroit

August 2019 — Present

- Developed Rest Web APIs and Micro Services in F#, and C#.NET
- Developed user interfaces with React and Angular
- Created CI/CD pipeline for SQL database deployments
- Deployed and hosted containerized applications with IaC in AWS
- Lead task force to rethink the organization's approach to on-call support
- · Mentored junior engineers

Apprentice Softare Developer at Ancor Utilitec, Troy

February 2017 — July 2019

- Front end website development implemented with C# .NET, HTML, CSS/ SASS, Javascript, JQuery
- · Back end website development implemented with C# .NET
- · Write stored procedures in SQL
- Database development in SQL
- Execute Functional and Regression Tests
- · Email development implemented with HTML, CSS, C# .NET and SQL

Chapter President and Secretary at Alpha Sigma Phi

December 2017 — December 2019

- Developed, deployed, and maintained a web-based fraternity content management system from scratch using PHP, JavaScript, MySQL, and a UNIX web server.
- Mentored younger members
- · Lead all organization meetings

EDUCATION

BA Computer Science, Oakland University, Auburn Hills

September 2015 — July 2022

One class left. 3.52 GPA.

■ REFERENCES

Alex Baldwin from Alex Baldwin LLC

832-477-8662

Anthony Chua from AccumTech

734-846-3097

Nick Hines from Ancor Utilitec

2487194086